const myCardsTitle = [
  {
    levelNumber: "4.2",
    title: "Uncountable nouns - some, any",
  },
];

const myCards = [
  {
    front: "Mam trochę czasu.",
    back: "I have some time.",
  },
  {
    front: "Czy masz trochę czasu?",
    back: "Do you have any time?",
  },
  {
    front: "Nie mam czasu.",
    back: "I don't have any time."
  },
  {
    front: "W lodówce jest trochę mleka.",
    back: "There is some milk in the fridge.",
  },
  {
    front: "Czy jest mleko w lodówce?",
    back: "Is there any milk in the fridge?",
  },
  {
    front: "W lodówce nie ma mleka.",
    back: "There isn't any milk in the fridge.",
  },
  {
    front: "Potrzebujemy informacji.",
    back: "We need some information.",
  },
  {
    front: "Czy potrzebujesz informacji?",
    back: "Do you need any information?",
  },
  {
    front: "Chcę kupić nowe meble.",
    back: "I want to buy some new furniture.",
  },
  {
    front: "Potrzebujesz nowych mebli?",
    back: "Do you need any new furniture?",
  },
  {
    front: "Nie potrzebuję nowych mebli.",
    back: "I don't need any new furniture.",
  },
  {
    front: "Oni chcą porady.",
    back: "They want some advice.",
  },
  {
    front: "Czy oni potrzebują porady?",
    back: "Do they need any advice?",
  },
  {
    front: "Nie potrzebują żadnych porad.",
    back: "They don't need any advice.",
  },
  {
    front: "Kupiłem trochę ryżu.",
    back: "I bought some rice.",
  },
  {
    front: "Kupiłeś ryż?",
    back: "Did you buy any rice?",
  },
  {
    front: "Nie kupiłem ryżu.",
    back: "I didn't buy any rice.",
  },
  {
    front: "On potrzebuje trochę czasu.",
    back: "He needs some time.",
  },
  {
    front: "Ona potrzebuje trochę przestrzeni.",
    back: "She needs some space.",
  },
  {
    front: "W butelce jest trochę wody.",
    back: "There's some water in the bottle.",
  },
  {
    front: "Czy w butelce jest woda?",
    back: "Is there any water in the bottle?",
  },
  {
    front: "W butelce nie ma wody.",
    back: "There isn't any water in the bottle.",
  },
  {
    front: "Czy możesz zrobić mi herbatę?",
    back: "Can you make me some tea?",
  },
  {
    front: "Czy możesz mi przynieść trochę soku?",
    back: "Could you bring me some juice?",
  },
  {
    front: "Czy możesz mi podać trochę chleba?",
    back: "Can you pass me some bread?",
  },
  {
    front: "Czy moglibyśmy dostać trochę makaronu?",
    back: "Could we get some pasta?",
  },
  {
    front: "Chciałbyś zjeść trochę zupy?",
    back: "Would you like to eat some soup?",
  },
  {
    front: "Czy mogę przynieść ci trochę wody?",
    back: "Can I get you some water?",
  },
  {
    front: "Chciałabyś trochę ciasta?",
    back: "Would you like some cake?",
  },
  {
    front: "Czy potrzebujesz pomocy?",
    back: "Would you like some help?",
  },
];
export { myCardsTitle, myCards };
